# **Amin NOROLLAH**

#### Contact

Phone:

+98 938 880 1636

**Email:** 

a.norollah.official@gmail.com

Website:

norollah.com

#### **Education**

Bachelor of engineering: computer engineering - 2014, Azad university

Master of science: computer engineering - 2019, IUST

# Languages

English – C1 Persian - Native

### **Honors**

Member of Iran's National Elites Foundation,

First Rank Student at IUST

#### Summary

I am a full-stack Senior Web Developer. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript, C#, HTML5, PHP OOP, CSS, SQL and NoSQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

# Skill Highlights

- Strong decision maker
- Project management
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

### **Experience**

Net Back-end developer at SarveenTech co. - Apr 2022 to Current Full-stack developer at Fara-control I.P co. – Aug 2021 to Current Graduated researcher at IUST – Jan 2019 to Apr 2022 NodeJS Back-end developer at ASI Green Techs – Sep 2021 to Feb 2022 Software Developer at Fara-control I.P co - Oct 2020 to Aug 2021 Freelance Software Developer – Mar 2019 to Oct 2021 Computer Engineer at Ultrasonic co. - Jan 2014 to Sep 2016

### Skills

| .Net framework   | C++, C#, WPF, WinForm, MVVM, Scichart, OOP  |
|------------------|---|
| .Net 6           | C#, SOLID, Security, Entity framework, Swagger, Microservice architecture, Identity server, and GraphQL |
| NodeJS           | JavaScript, ExpressJS, Mongoose, Pug and Swagger  |
| Angular          | Typescript, RxJS, Angular CLI, Angular Material, HTML, and CSS  |
| ReactJS (Casual) | JavaScript, Redux, HTML, Bootstrap and CSS  |
| Databases        | MongoDB, Microsoft SQL server, Ignite, SQLite, and Postgre  |
| Design           | Photoshop, CorelDraw, and Figma   |

### **My Open-Source Projects**

PAT-Noxim, RTHS, SAFAS, JS-code, Identity server, CSite front-end, and CSite back-end.

(Please visit my website for more information.)









